the Fibonacci sequence starts with fub1
equal to 1 so f1^ squar is the area of a
1x1 Square FS2 is also equal to 1 so FS2
^2 is the area of a 1x one square as
well when n is greater than two the nth
Fibonacci number is the sum of the
previous two Fibonacci numbers notice we
can keep attaching squares to this
diagram in such a way that the side
length is the sum of the previous two
Fibonacci numbers and is therefore for
the next Fibonacci number so as we add
squares to this diagram the I Square
will have an area given by this square
of the I Fibonacci number we can
continue this process as long as we like
if we eventually stop say at the number
F subn then we have a rectangular
diagram enclosing an area given by the
sum of the squares of the first n
Fibonacci numbers on the other hand the
dimensions of this rectangular diagram
are the N Fibonacci number by the N plus
1 Fibonacci number so the enclosed area
is the product of these two numbers this
means that the sum of the squares of the
first n Fibonacci numbers is the product
of two consecutive Fibonacci numbers